我没有理由沮丧
I have no reason to frown
我不需要转过身
I don't need to turn around
现在哭还有何用
What's the use in crying now
我不敢相信所见
I can't believe my eyes
我撒了一个瞒天大谎
I told myself the perfect lie
但我现在已不想死掉
But I don't feel like dying now
即使我给自己安排
最厄的运
And even though I turned the odds
against myself
我发现我又再次被
他人所救
Again I find that I've been saved
by someone else
所以今晚，我会改过重来
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂为何
我会想要独自吞泪
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以来，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在这
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在这
All I need's right here
有人说我疯狂
Some say I lost my mind
至少我终于学会了
at least I found it given time
我再也不这样脆弱
I won't go down so easily
对啦，我知道很明显
Yeah, it's easy enough to admit
我本来就是不适合
it never was a perfect fit
那月球还是太小了
The moon is just too small for me
所以今晚，我会改过重来
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂为何
我会想要独自吞泪
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以来，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在这
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在这
All I need's right here
所以今晚，我会改过重来
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂为何
我会想要独自吞泪
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
所以今晚，我会改过重来
So tonight, I will make it right
我仍不懂为何
我会想要独自吞泪
Still I don't know why
I thought I'd swallow all my tears
一直以来，我都想得太歪
All along, I was thinking wrong
我花太久搞清
我所需就在这
It took me far too long to see that
all I need's right here
我所需就在这
All I need's right here